staffino.com 2014-03-07

# Privacy Policy

Your privacy is critically important to us. Our privacy policy will explain how personal information is collected, used and disclosed with respect to your access and use of Staffino’s web site, mobile application and services (“Staffino ”).

If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at hello@staffino.com.

Our privacy policy may be modified from time-to-time. We will alert you that changes have been made by indicating on our privacy policy the date it was last updated. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email or by means of a notice on this web site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

### What is Personal Information?

"Personal Information” is personally identifiable information such as your name, telephone number and email address and any other non-public information about you that is associated with or linked to any of the foregoing information. Personal information does not include "aggregate" information, which is data we collect about the use of Staffino. Our privacy policy does not restrict or limit our collection and use of aggregate information.

### What Personal Information Do We Collect?

We actively collect certain information you voluntarily provide to us including but not limited to:

  * 1) your name,
  * 2) email address,

We automatically collect certain information when you use Staffino, such as:

  * 1) your Internet Protocol (IP) address,
  * 2) your device type, and
  * 3) your operating system version.

We treat this information as personal information if we combine it with or link it to any of the identifying information mentioned above. Otherwise, it is used in the aggregate only.

When you download and use our Services, we automatically collect information on:

  * 1) the type of device you use,
  * 2) operating system version,
  * 3) and the device identifier (or "UDID").

We also collect your location-based information for the purpose of:

  * 1) attaching location information while finding venues nearby

### How Do We Use the Personal Information We Collect?

Generally, we collect, store, use and disclose information to enable us to:

  * 1) provide Staffino,
  * 2) create your account,
  * 3) identify you as a user,
  * 4) respond to your feedback,
  * 5) improve the Staffino,
  * 6) send you administrative and service related communications,
  * 7) and send you newsletters, surveys, offers, and other promotional materials.

Except as set out in this Privacy Policy, your Personal Information will not be used for any other purpose without informing you first by updating this Privacy Policy.

Except for the limited disclosures described in this Privacy Policy, we do not sell customer lists or any personal information to third parties, and we will endeavor to keep your email address private.

Anonymous aggregate statistics that do not personally identify a Staffino user will be kept and used by us for various purposes including analysis and reporting of usage patterns. Staffino reserves the right to use and disclose anonymous aggregate statistics for any purpose and to any third party in its sole discretion. 

### What Do We Share With Third Parties?

From time to time we may employ third parties to help us provide or improve Staffino. These third parties, such as our analytics or hosting provider, may have limited access to databases of user information or registered member information solely for the purpose of helping us provide or improve the Staffino and they will not be able to use the information about our members or visitors for any other purpose.

We may disclose Personal Information in some other limited circumstances, but we will specifically describe them to you when we collect the information, such as in the terms of use for a new service or by revising this Privacy Policy.

We may, and you hereby authorize us to, disclose your Personal Information (including messages) to a third party without your consent:

  * a) if we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our rights or property, other website users, or anyone else (including the rights or property of anyone else) that could be harmed by such activities,
  * b) in connection with any legal investigation,
  * c) when we believe in good faith that such disclosure is required by and in accordance with the law or to respond to subpoenas or warrants served on Staffino,
  * d) to any third party with your prior consent to do so.

### Control Over Content

Aside from what is set forth in our privacy policy, we will store any content submitted to Staffino for the sole purpose of displaying that content only to the person with whom you are paired, or for whom you are currently waiting to accept your pair request, at the time of submission. Your content will only be accessed by Staffino employees for the purposes of technical support. When you make a request for technical support that may require us to access your content, we will notify you and seek permission before accessing your timeline.

### Links to Other Sites

When you click on a link to any other website or location, you will leave Staffino and go to another site and another entity may collect Personal Information or anonymous data from you. We have no control over, do not review, and cannot be responsible for, these outside websites or their content. Please be aware that the terms of this Privacy Policy do not apply to these outside websites or content, or to any collection of data after you click on links to such outside websites.

### Security

The security of your Personal Information is important to us. We use reasonable efforts to store and maintain your Personal Information and location information in a secure environment and have implemented reasonable procedures designed to limit unauthorized access, use or disclosure of your Personal Information. We encrypt the transmission location information of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

You are also responsible for helping to protect the security of your Personal Information. To protect the communications that have taken place in the app, never give out your password. To increase device-level security, set a Security Code in the Staffino’s settings.

## User Access and Choice

If your personal information changes, or if you no longer desire our service , you may email us at hello@staffino.com to deactivate your account. You may also correct, update, or amend your personal information in your profile settings within Staffino.

Removing Staffino from your mobile device will not delete the personal information we have retained about you. If you unpair from your partner, we will retain your user content in the event that you would like to access in the future. Your user content can be deleted permanently by emailing a request to hello@staffino.com.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

### Tracking Technologies We Collect

We use cookies on this site. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personal information you submit while on our site.

  * 1) We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies.
  * 2) A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A session ID cookie remembers that you are logged in.
  * 3) A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. A persistent cookie saves your individual preferences next time that you log in. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “Help” directory.

If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site, such as contests or surveys, will be limited.

The use of cookies by our partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers is not covered by our privacy statement. We do not have access or control over these cookies. Our partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers use session ID cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site.

Our third party partners employ clear gifs, images, and scripts that help them better manage content on our site. We do not tie the information gathered to our users personal information.

### Questions?

Please contact us at hello@staffino.com if you have any questions about our privacy policy.
